뭐가 우위랑 운율이 맞지?
아무것도 없어
What rhymes with majority?
Nothing.
설마 아직도 새 의장에 대한 코미디
송을 쓰고 있는 거에요?
Come on, you still working on that
funny song about the new Speaker?
그만 좀 해요
아, 우선순위
- Give it a break.
- Oh, priority.
그리고 권위
And authority.
Sorority.
이럴수가 운율이 쏟아져나오고 있어!
Oh, my God, there's a million
words that rhyme with it.
안돼, 안돼 이럴 순 없어! 젠장!
Oh, no.
No, no, no! Gah!
조나가 어디서 오는지 보세요
Look where Jonah's coming from.
저 히죽거리는 얼굴에, 키까지 흔들면서
빌어먹을
Oh, that grin, the keys.
Oh, God.
백악관 전용 주차공간을
받았나 보구만
He's been given
West Exec parking.
빌어먹을 성배를 꿰어찼네요
그래봐야 주차장이지만요
Yeah, the holy grail
of parking.
좋은 아침입니다 여러분
이 얼마나 즐거운 날인지요
Good morning, gentlemen.
What a delightful day.
저도 여러분처럼 걸어서
출근하려고 했습니다만 생각해보니...
I was gonna walk
to work, but then...
너따위가 백악관 주차공간을 받았다고?
그냥 주차공간일 뿐이야 댄
- You got West Exec?
- It's just a parking spot, Dan.
그런 거에 질투한다면 넌 정말
얄팍한 뭐랄까...
To be jealous of that, you'd
have to be a shallow kind of...
뭐드라... 아 맞다 병신이겠네
I don't know, dick, I guess.
지난번 인질구출 임무 수행시
상황실 사진입니다 부통령님
This is the situation room, ma'am,
during the hostage mission.
이중에서 배포될 사진을 골라야 합니다
알았어
- We need to approve a photo for release.
- Okay.
좀 볼까
Let's see.
빌어먹을, 벤 좀 봐봐
Oh, my God.
Look at Ben.
빌어먹을 커피 머그잔
크기 좀 보소
Look at the size
of his coffee mug.
무슨 애 하나 집어넣을만한
걸 들고 다니네
Jeez, you could hide
a baby in that thing.
그래도 나는 잘 나왔다 그지?
Ooh, I look nice, though, huh?
예 정말 그렇네요
Yeah, you do.
걱정스러우면서도 강인해 보이세요
You look concerned, but steely.
글치
완전 여전사 필이네요
- Yeah.
- Like a lady soldier.
그리고 내일 십대 조찬 기도회 행사때
Oh, there are not
gonna be any veterans
퇴역군인들은 안 오겠지?
at this teen prayer breakfast
thing tomorrow, are there?
아닙니다 각하 모두 다리가
제자리에 달려 있을 겁니다
No, ma'am.
No missing legs.
내일 만나보실 젊은
리더들에 대한
Okay, here's all the details
of the youth leaders
세부사항이 모두 여기에 있습니다
세상에
- that you're gonna be meeting.
- Oh, man.
도대체 뭐하는 놈이길래
십대때부터 종교에 심취했데?
Who the hell is religious
as a teenager?
저도 그랬는데요
I was.
대마라도 좀 빨던가 하란 말야
정말 어이가 없어서, 그치?
I mean, smoke some weed,
for Christ's sake, right?
이런 젠장 대통령 좀 봐
Oh, God, look at the president.
젠장 완전...
턱쟁이죠
- Jeez, he looks so...
- He looks jowly.
맙소사 볼때기 좀 보세요
Ah, look at those cheeks.
무슨 클러치백을 얼굴 양쪽에
붙여놓은 것 같네요
It's like two little clutch
bags attached to his face.
맙소사 또 가방얘기네
넌 항상 가방얘기야 게리
Oh, my God, with the bags.
It's always bags with you.
가방에 대한 집착을 버리라구
Got to get out of the bag zone.
알겠지 게리?
Come on, Gary.
- Sir.
- Gentlemen.
이번에 새로 시도하시는 인구조사
연구가 굉장히 흥미롭더군요
Very excited about this new
demographics study you're planning.
그렇겠지 꿈의 측량법이
선거전의 지형을 정확히 밝혀낼 테니까 말이지
You should be.
Dream Metric will reveal
the electoral battleground
as it truly is.
현미경의 발명과 맞먹는
성과라고나 할까
It's comparable to the
invention of the microscope.
제가 가진 선거 전략에 대한
생각을 좀 보여드려도 될까요?
Would it be okay if I showed you some
ideas I have regarding strategy?
그럴 시간 없네
No time, Mr. Egan.
거의 다 플래쉬지만 유튜브에도 올려놨습니다
They're mostly Flash based,
but I put them on YouTube.
방금 말했듯이 그럴 시간 없네
I just said I had no time.
우리 모두 지켜야할 마감시간이
있는 법이니말야 그렇지 않나 마이크?
We're all being hit
by deadlines, right, Mike?
그렇습니다, 돛의 활대처럼
지랄맞은 게 바로 마감이죠
Yes, sir. They can swing around
and smack you like a boom.
자네도 배를 타나 마이크?
보트가 있어?
You sail, Mike?
Have a boat?
어 예 그렇습니다 87년 걸프스타 50입니다
좋은 크루저로군
- Uh, yes, sir. An '87 Gulfstar 50.
- Great cruiser.
화려한 건 아닙니다만 요구되는
성능은 다 갖추고 있죠
Nothing fancy,
but she gets the job done.
주철 냄비나 케빈 베이컨처럼 말이죠
You know, like a cast-iron
skillet or Kevin Bacon.
난 라군 380이라네
I've got a Lagoon 380.
쌍동형 말입니까?
맞아
- Catamaran?
- Yeah.
진정난 남자의 항해란 그런 거죠
That's real man's sailing.
배에 기대어 바닷 물결을 맞으며 말이죠
Leaning out in the tack, your big
man balls dipping in the salty sea.
그말대로야
You're right there,
my friend, yeah.
난 자식이 없고 바라지도 않지만
I have no children
and I wish for none,
그녀는 내 가족이라네
but she's my family.
저도 예전에 이리 호로
파워보팅하러 간 적이 있었죠
You know, I once went
powerboating on Lake Erie.
급류가 장난이 아니더군요
Amazing rush.
난 그만 가봐야 겠네
I need to go.
우리같은 항해자한테는 파워보팅을
언급하는 게 아니야 댄
You don't talk powerboating
to us sailors, Dan.
도대체 뭐가 그렇게 다른데요?
What's the fucking difference?
안녕, 부통령께선 계셔?
Hey. Veep in?
아니
벌써 거기에 앉아있을 시간이 되냐?
- - No.
You have time to just sit there?
여기 사람이 얼만데 주차공간 얘기로
거만떨 사람이 벌써 다 떨어졌단 말야?
You've already bugged the shit out
of everyone else in the building?
미안 못 들었네
다시 좀 말해보지?
I'm sorry, what?
Say that again.
꺼져 조나, 아니면 내 후춧가루
스프레이가 작동하는지 시험해 볼테니까
Jonah, out. Or else I'll see
if my pepper spray works.
- Morning, guys.
- Morning.
만삼천, 아니다만사천오백
13,000.
No, 14,500.
그게 니가 오늘 거울을 바라보면서
나르시즘에 빠진 횟순가보지?
Is this the amount of times you've
admired yourself in the mirror today?
아뇨, 아마 그게 방금 면접받고 온
회사와 지금 직장의
No, I'm guessing that's
the difference in salary
월급차가 아닐까 해서요
between this job and the one
that you just interviewed for.
내가 면접을 본 것 같다고?
You think I had
a job interview?
같은 게 아니라 확신이에요
I know you had a job interview.
이유를 들어보실까 셜록?
간결한 화장에, 목선도 높게 잠궜고
- How, Sherlock?
- Simple makeup, higher neckline.
굽 낮은 신발은 그 드레스랑 안 어울려요
그말은 하이힐이 가방 안에 있다는 얘기죠
Flats don't go with that dress, which means
you probably have heels in your bag.
모퉁이 빵집에서 산 커피는
당신이 18번가 로비스트 펌에 있었다는 걸 암시하죠
Coffee from corner bakery
implying you were at
one of the lobbying
shops on 18th.
존나 짜릿하네
I love this stuff.
그리고 당신이 정확한
주소를 알고 있는지 확인하려고
That and somebody
called your extension
당신 자리로 전화가 왔었거든요
to make sure you had
the right address.
오늘 대니 청도 공연하게 될까?
Hey, is Danny Chung gonna be performing
tonight?
정말?
걔가 도대체 뭐가 있다고?
Really?
What's he gonna be doing?
지가 조또 전쟁영웅이라는
걸 우리가 한시라도 잊지 못하도록
I think he'll be pulling Bon
Jovi out of a burning tank
불타는 탱크에 대한 본조비
짓을 하거나 그러겠죠
in case we all forgot what
a fucking war hero he is.
공식적인 코멘트는 없습니다
- Yeah.
- No, we have no official comment.
아니 그건 '노 코멘트'가 아니에요
No, that is not
a non-comment.
그냥 코멘팅을 하지 않는 겁니다
뭐?
- We're just not commenting.
- What?
이 사진이 어떻게 나간 겁니까?
뭐라고?
- How did this photo get out there?
- What?
그럼 인터넷에서 지울 수 있는건가요?
Can we delete it
off the Internet, then?
아뇨 나도 내가 무슨 개소리를
하는지 전혀 몰라요
No, I don't know
what I'm talking about.
뭐야? 무슨 일인 건데?
What?
What's going on here?
부통령님, 백악관에서
이 사진을 배포했어요
Ma'am, the White House
released this picture.
뭐라고? 노, 안돼
이건 내가 고른게...
What? No, no.
This isn't...
에이미 이건 내가 승인한
사진이 아니잖아
Amy, this isn't the photo
that we approved.
절대 아니죠
이걸 좀 봐
- No.
- Look at this.
군인 다리가 날아갔을 때
난 트위터나 한 것처럼 보이잖아
It looks like I'm tweeting
when a guy loses his leg.
그렇습니다 각하
Yeah, it does, ma'am.
이건 켄트 짓이야
This is Kent's doing.
그 자식이 날 엿먹이고 있어
배때지에 칼을 꼽아버려야지
He's trying to screw me.
I'm gonna go stab him.
진심으로 내장을 후벼버릴거야
I'm stabbing him.
그래 현 시점에서는 아주
됐고, 모두 나가
- Yeah, from this point. It's unprec...
- All right, get out.
꺼지라고
너도야 에이미
Get out.
You, too, Amy.
여기 목격자가 있어선 안된다고
나 지금 농담하는 게 아냐
I don't want any witnesses in here.
I'm not kidding.
전 염산욕조를 만들어 놓을게요
좋아
- I'll start running the acid bath.
- Yeah.
사진 때문에 이러는 겁니까?
This is the photograph?
아니, 그냥 내 스웨터가 드레스랑
어울리는지 물어보려고 그런다
No, just wondering if you think
this sweater goes with the dress.
보세요, 다른 사진들은
대통령님을 이상한 각도로 잡았어요
Look, the other photos
caught POTUS at a bad angle.
그 턱 말입니다
뭐라고?
- Vis-A?-vis jowls.
- What?
이상하게 나왔다고요
그게 그양반 생긴 모냥이야 원래 그런 쌍판이라고
- It's a bad look.
- That's how he looks. That's his face.
그럼 내가 잘나온 사진을 컨트롤 C
해서 이거에 페이스트라도 하던가
Why didn't you just take the
good one of me, Photoshop it in?
제가 역사를 에어브러싱할 수는 없는 노릇이죠
제가 무슨 스탈린도 아니고
I can't airbrush history, ma'am.
I'm not Joseph Stalin.
맞아 그건 사실이지
넌 스탈린이 아냐
No, that's true.
You're not.
넌 씨바 스탈린의
십분의 일도 매력적이지 않거든
You don't have
a tenth of his charm.
됐고 난 이제 가서 짐 마우드(의장)
노래나 마무리해야겠어
Okay, I'm just gonna go work
on my Jim Marwood song.
어... 우린 지금 예산안을 협의중이고
초당적 지원이 필요한 상태입니다
Uh, we're in budget talks,
reaching across the aisle.
대통령께선 하원의장을
놀리는 걸 바라지 않으세요
POTUS does not want
the Speaker mocked.
오, 그럼 이제 댄이랑 마이크
Oh, so now I have
to have Dan and Mike,
로저스 & 해머쉿(원래는 해머스타인)
한테 오후까지 새 노래를 쓰라고 해야겠네?
Rodgers and Hammershit, come up
with a new song in an afternoon?
우리 스스로를 대상으로 하는
것도 나쁘진 않겠죠
We can laugh at ourselves.
이번 사진에 대해 좀 농담을
해보시던가요
Maybe you should do a funny
bit about the photograph.
상황을 장악하는거에요
이거나 먹어라
- Own the situation.
- Own this.
멀티태스킹 중이었다고
전화 좀 끊어봐
- She was multitasking.
- You need to get off the phone.
여자라면 당연히 할 수 있는 거라고
좋은 냄새를 풍기면서 선물을 포장하는 것처럼
It's a thing women can do, like
smelling nice and wrapping gifts.
됐고
잘있어 탐
- Okay.
- Bye, Tom.
지금 제대로 하고 있는 거야 뭐야?
Were you on top
of this or what?
저희는 하원의장에 대한 코미디 송에
We were busy writing
youth culture references
십대가 알아먹을 만한
걸 넣으려고 고민중이었어요
in a funny song
about the Speaker.
블라브라블라디코파블라
뭐라 카는지도 모르겠네
I don't even know
what you just said.
넌 또 뭘 웃고 있어
좇물면상 멀대 새끼야
What are you laughing about,
Jolly Green Jizzface?
전 그냥... 죄송합니다 매앰
빌어먹을 애시당초에 왜 여기 있는데?
- I was... sorry, ma'am.
- God damn, why are you even here?
오 미임이 되신 걸 알려드리려고
왔습니다 매앰
Oh, I came here to tell you
that you're a meme, ma'am.
내가 미임 매앰이라고? 도대체 뭔 헛소리야?
빌어먹을 영어를 쓰란 말야 새캬
I'm a meme ma'am? What are you talking about?
Speak English, boy.
미임입니다, 인터넷 현상이죠
A meme, an Internet phenomenon.
그렇네요 트위터에 이 사진의
Okay, yes. There are
Photoshopped versions of this
포샵버전들이 난무하고 있어요
springing up all over Twitter.
독립선언과 부통령
- You at the Declaration of Independence...
- Oh, my God.
메리 막달레나와 십자가형과 부통령
With Mary Magdalene
at the crucifixion,
2004년 쓰나미와 부통령
the 2004 tsunami.
만약 쓰나미가 닥친다면 실제로
폰을 보고 있을 거에요
If there was a tsunami, you'd be
genuinely looking at your phone
날씨를 확인해봐야 할 것 아니에요
'cause you'd be checking
the weather.
그냥 좀 닥치고 있어
You know what?
I don't need you to talk.
이 미임 매앰 지랄을
어떻게 멈추는데?
How do we stop
this meme ma'am shit?
아뇨 그냥 미임입니다 매앰
미임 매앰이 아니구요
No, it's just a meme, ma'am.
Not a meme ma'am.
그리고 보통 48시간이 지나면
다 불타오르고 자연소멸하죠
And usually they flame out
after about 48 hours,
하지만 때로는 불타올라서
슈퍼 미임이 되기도 합니다
but sometimes they blow up
and become a super meme
강남스타일처럼 말이죠
like Downfall or Gangnam.
난 그거 좋던데
내가 뭐랬지?
- I love Gangnam.
- What did I just say?
레딧이나 텀블러까지 가면
그럴 수도 있죠
If it gets on Reddit
or Tumblr, that can happen.
좋아 됐고
넌 이제 당장 꺼지는 거야 알았지?
Yeah, okay.
You've got to get out of here, okay?
그 빌어먹을 의미도 없는 음절들을
데리고 꺼저버리라고
Take all these meaningless syllables
with you and just get out.
예 물론이죠 각하
아 그리고 오늘 저녘 때 뵙겠습니다
Yes, absolutely, ma'am.
Oh, and I will see you at the dinner tonight.
아 젠장할
Oh, my God, yeah.
이 빌어먹을 똥케익 위에
꽂힌 마지막 한방이구만
Okay, yeah, that's a cherry
on top of this whole turd cake.
윽, 니 다리
그거 좀...?
Ooh, your leg.
Could you put...?
내가 니 다리를 전부 볼 수
있게 자세 좀 바꿔볼래?
Fix your leg so I can
see your whole leg.
고치라고 좋아
Fix it. Yeah.
Okay.
포투스가 우리는 하원의장에
대한 노래를 하는 걸 금지했어
POTUS said that we can't do
the song about the Speaker
빅 앨런 디너에서 말야
우린 그거 못해
at the Vic Allen dinner.
We can't do it.
하원의장 노래가 잘렸다구요?
그래
- The Speaker song is cut?
- Yeah.
완전 빵터졌는데
그정돈 아니고
- It was hilarious.
- It was not that hilarious.
씨발 지금 정신이 있냐? 웃다가
완전 질질 쌌을 거라고
You're out of your head, dude. That would
have made people piss in their pants.
Hey, hey, hey!
켄트에 관한 노래를 만들면 어때요?
Let's do a new song about Kent.
켄트?
- Kent?
- Mm-hmm.
그게 좋을 것 같아?
자기자신을 조롱해보자, 켄트가 직접 한 말이죠
- You think?
- Make fun of ourselves, that's what he said.
사실 그거 괜찮을 것 같아
I kind of like that.
사실 정말로 마음에 들어
I do, I kind of like that.
좋아 그걸로 가는거야
난 전혀 문제 없어 그걸로 가자고
All right, we'll do it.
I have no problem with that. Let's go.
그렇게 해보자고
That's what we're gonna do.
Let's go.
필리버스터를 멈추자 버스터
Just stop
the filibuster, buster.
아주 괜춘한데
그건 운율이 아니야
- That's good.
- That's not a rhyme.
그냥 단어를 같은 단어로
맞추는 거잖아
You're just matching a word
with the same word.
그냥 좀 적어놔봐 댄
나 지금 완전 꽂혔다고
Just write it down, Dan.
I'm in a zone.
코미디 송은 개객끼의 상징이라고
Comedy songs are the mark
of a douchebag.
그렇지 않아
왜 그런지 알아?
You're wrong.
You know why?
세 마디야...
위어드 알 양코빅이지
Three words...
Weird Al Yankovic.
조또 알 양코쉿같은
Shit Al Yankoshit.
입 좀 닥치라고 알겠어?
You shut your mouth, okay?
그냥 좀 닥...
멸종위기 거위 구하기 브루스라든가
Just... protect the endangered
goose, Bruce.
모두 훌륭하다고 "연인을 떠나는 50가지 방법"
의 패러디 송이지
These are all great. A parody song
of "50 Ways to Leave Your Lover."
환상적인 아이디어라고
진심으로요?
- Great idea.
- Really?
그래
만약 첫번째가 별로면
- Yeah.
- If the first one bombs,
사람들은 모두 "씨바 이런 게
앞으로 49개나 남았단 말야"
people are gonna be
sitting out there thinking,
이러면서 앉아있을 거라고요
"Shit the bed, we got
49 more of these to go."
석유 로비를 도와줘 바비
이것도 좋지
Help the oil lobby, Bobby.
That's a good one.
조나를 따라가보죠
Let's follow Jonah.
완전 유치한 짓이군
That is so childish.
도대체 왜 이런 걸 하는 건데?
Why are we doing this?
왜냐면 조또 의미가 없기 때문이죠
우리가 하는 일이 다 그런 거잖아요
Because it's pointless, like
everything else that we do.
켄트랑 어울릴 수 없어서
아직도 짜증내고 있는 거야?
You still pissed
you can't get in with Kent?
아무도 못 어울려 그작자는
반은 로봇에 나머지 반도 로봇이라고
Nobody can.
He's half robot, half robot.
순도 100%의 로봇이야
그게 바로 도전의 묘미에요 마이크
- He's a robot.
- Yeah, that's the challenge, Mike.
그러니까 내 대학시절
모든 여자애들은 나를 좋아했어요
See, in college
all the girls liked me.
다만 딱 한명 아주 영리하고
나한테 관심이 없는 여자애가 있었죠
There was this one girl, smart,
who had no interest in me.
레즈비언도 아니었고요
제가 체크해봤죠
She wasn't gay either.
I checked.
그래서 걔를 따먹는 게 저의
지상과제가 되었어요
So it became my mission
to sleep with her.
그래서 성공했어?
And did you?
아뇨
No.
그리고 그 실패가 지금까지도
저를 옭아매고 고통스럽게 해요
And that failure has haunted
me to this very day.
나도 비슷한 경험담이 있지
하지만 방향은 정반대야
I have a similar story,
but the other way around.
대학시절 딱 한 여자만 나한테
관심이 있었는데 알고보니 레즈비언이더군
In college there was only one
girl that was interested in me.
And it turns out
she was actually a lesbian.
모두 좀 사기가 떨어졌어요
Everyone is a little off.
>
댄은 지루해하고 있고 수는
다른 직장을 알아보고 있어요
Dan is bored.
Sue is looking for another job.
뭐? 레알?
What? Really?
예, 그리고 개리한테
하시는 말씀이 좀......
Mmm, and the stuff
you're saying to Gary...
뭐? 개리가 나한테 불만이 있다고?
What?
Gary's not happy with me?
진짜?
What?
걔는 내가 면상에 총을
갈겨도 행복할 애인데
Because he'd be happy
if I shot him in the face.
그럴거야
내가 진지하게 생각을 해 봤다고
He would be.
I've actually thought about it.
개리는 자기가 여친이
생긴 이후로
He feels since he got
that girlfriend Dana,
부통령님께서 자기한테 심하다고
생각하고 있어요
you've been weird with him.
잠깐 그거 좀....
그러니까 좀 그러지좀....
Okay, can you please...
can you please not...
보셨죠? 그게 제가 하려는 말이에요
다리요
See? That is another thing.
The leg.
걔가 다리를 통째로 잃은 게 사실이잖아
Well, he did lose a whole leg.
2짝있던 다리가 외다리가
되어버린 거라고
That's like half of what
he should have, right?
난 괜찮아, 내가 다 잘
할 수 있다고
I'm fine. Look, I can
handle this whole thing.
할 수 있어
수
I can.
Sue.
넌 이곳에서 굉장히 중요한 존재이고
니가 여기를 떠나지 않게 하기 위해서
You are incredibly valued
here and I was wondering
우리가 할 수 있는 일이 없을까
해서 물어보는 거야
if there's anything we could do
to make you want to stay with us.
봉급인상이죠 각하
내가 어떻게 해 볼게 돌아온 걸 축하해
- More money, ma'am.
- I'm on it. Welcome back.
모시게 되어 영광입니다
Honored to serve.
방금 수를 푼돈으로 매수했고
다음은 누구지?
Just bought Sue for a dollar.
Who's next?
개리요
내가 게리한테 말해볼게
- Gary.
- I'll talk to Gary.
밖에서 얘기해보시는 건 어떨까요?
How about doing that
outside of the office?
저녘 식사에 초대하신다든가요
Invite him to dinner maybe.
와우, 생각해보니 한번도
같이 식사한 적이 없어
Wow. I've never eaten
with Gary before.
옆에서 먹은 적이 있긴 하지만 그건...
I've eaten next to him, but...
좋아 괜찮네 그럴 수 있지
Okay, yeah.
I can do that.
좋은 아침이야 좇나
한심한 시키
- Good morning, Jonad.
- You're pathetic.
조방울
Jonuts!
다음에 사무실이 생기면
그때 다시 찾아오라고 알겠지?
Yeah, come at me when you guys
get an office, huh?
모조리 다 조나를 싫어하네요
그래, 하지만 우리가 원조야
- Everyone hates him.
- Yeah, but we hated him first.
물론이죠 우리는 조나를 싫어하는 게
쿨해지기 전부터도 싫어했잖아요
Oh, yeah, we hated him long before
it was even fashionable to hate him.
무슨 야생 다큐멘터리 같아
This is like a
wildlife documentary.
조나의 야생서식지를 찾는 거지
조나가 덤불 속에 똥을 쌀지도 모르죠
Jonah in his natural habitat.
He might defecate in a bush.
이게 뭐지
나도 몰라
- What is this?
- I don't know.
조나
안녕
- Jonah.
- Hey.
바빠?
아니
- Busy?
- No.
그냥 이 블라이던 클립을
가지러 온 거야
I just had to get
some of these binder clips.
오
다른 빌딩에서부터 말야?
- Oh.
- From another building, huh?
그래 백악관에서는
다 떨어졌거든
Yeah, we ran out
at the White House.
하지만 그런 거 담당하는
사람이 있지 않나?
Isn't there a guy, though,
that can get that for you?
분명히 그런 사람이 있을 텐데
Yeah, you'd think
there would be.
그래 그런데 그 사람이
아파서 못 나왔어
Yeah, but he's...
he's off sick.
누가?
스티브
- Who is?
- Steve.
불쌍한 늙은 스티브가
뭘로 아픈 거지?
What's poor old Steve
come down with?
당뇨야
오 와우 그거 심각하네
- He has diabetes.
- Oh, wow. That's a big one.
몇긴데?
2기야
- What type?
- Two.
2기 당뇨의 증상이 뭐였지?
Yeah. What are the
symptoms of two again?
아 그냥 몸이 좋지 않데
Oh, he's just feeling bad.
그는 그러니까, 당분말야
He's... you know,
he's sugary.
그래
당분이 충분하지 않데
- Yeah.
- Or he's not sugary enough.
그렇지
그래
- Right.
- Yeah.
다른 증상은 없고?
Are there any other symptoms?
그래 손목도 굵어지고
뭐 그런 거 있잖아
Yeah, he's got fat wrists.
You know?
너도 켄트한테 밀려났냐?
Yeah. You getting
freezed out by Kent?
우리는 널 따라왔어 조나
We've been watching you, Jonah.
넌 완전히 밀려난거야
You're obsolete.
넌 이제 VCR 신세인 거지
물론 입도 더 크고 말야
You're like an old VCR,
but with a bigger mouth.
날 따라왔다고?
그래
- You guys have been following me?
- Yeah.
낸시 드류랑 킁킁대는 개처럼
날 미행해놓고
You've been following me like Nancy
Drew and his butt-sniffing dog
나보고 할일이 없다고?
and I'm the one
that has nothing to do?
웃기시네 우린 완전 바빠
Cool the honey, bro.
We're very busy.
우린 코믹 송을 쓰고 있다고
닥쳐요 마이크
- We're writing a comical song.
- Shut up, Mike.
뭐, 내 비록 할일은 없을지 몰라도
Well, I might have
nothing to do, gentlemen,
적어도 내가 그거에 대해 한탄을 할 땐
but at least
when I'm crying about it,
웨스트 윙 전용 주차장에 주차한
I am crying about it in my car
내 차 안에서 울 수 있다는 거야
in West Wing Exec parking.
♪ 50 ways to win in Denver ♪
덴버에서 이길 수 있는 50가지 방법
♪ La-lum. ♪
각하 절 저녘식사에 초대해
주신 거에 대해 다시 한번 감사드립니다
Hey, ma'am, thanks again
for inviting me to dinner.
그래
영광이에요
- Sure.
- It's an honor.
이 사건을 일기장에 써놓고 오분을
내리 응시하고 있었다니까요
I actually wrote it in my diary and
stared at it for a full five minutes.
♪ My treat for you... ♪
내가 대접할게
♪ Would you set it
all up, please ♪
전부 준비좀 해줄래
♪ Would you set it
all up, please ♪
♪ And check the menu, too? ♪
메뉴도 좀 체크하고 말이야?
♪ Of course. ♪
물론입죠
♪ No, no, no, I actually
really do mean that ♪
아니 나 지금 진담이야
♪ No, no, no, I actually
really do mean that ♪
♪ Figure out the restaurant
and everything. ♪
레스토랑이랑 메뉴도 전부
찾아서 에약해놔
♪ Figure out the restaurant
and everything. ♪
그래야죠
Okay. Okay.
- Um, do you...
- ♪ Yes, Gary? ♪
어 저기...
왜그러는데 개리야
- Um, do you...
- * Yes, Gary? *
♪ What is it? ♪
뭔 일인데>
♪ Can Dana come along? ♪
데이나도 같이 와도 될까요?
어 정말?
아뇨
- Oh, really?
- No.
좋지 않은 생각이었어요
That was a bad idea.
안 됀다면 그것도 물론 괜찮아요
It's okay if she can't.
아냐, 괜찮아
Um, no, it's good.
Fine.
데이나가 정말 마음에 드실 거예요
You are gonna love her.
완전히 여자들한테 사랑받는 애거든요
오, 완전 기대되네
- She's a total gal's gal.
- Oh, I can't wait.
그녀가 말하기를...
내 목 스프레이 좀 줄래?
- She says this one thing...
- Can you get me my throat spray?
그게 필요하거든 가지고 있어?
물론이죠
- I need that. Do you have it?
- Sure.
♪ Mi fa so la ti do. ♪
미파솔라시도
* Mi fa so la ti do. *
♪ No, no, no,
don't sing it with me ♪
노 노 노 나랑 같이 부르지 마
* No, no, no,
don't sing it with me *
♪ That fucks me up. ♪
완전 엉망이 된다고
짐
부통령 각하
- Jim.
- Madam Vice President.
전 항상 절(다리를 뒤로 빼는 여성용 인사)을
해야 할 것 같다는 생각이 들어요
I always feel
like I should curtsy,
그리고서는 그게 얼마나 어처구니
없는 일인지 기억해내죠
and then I remember
that doesn't make sense.
그렇죠 아주 이상한 일이죠
No, it certainly does not.
에이미 브룩하이머 아시죠?
제 비서실장이에요
You know Amy Brookheimer,
my chief of staff.
하원의장님 다시 뵈어 반갑습니다
Mr. Speaker.
It's nice to see you again.
에이미, 내가 늙어가는 건가
아니면 자네가 젊어지는 건가?
Amy. Now, am I getting older
or are you getting younger?
우리 모두 나이를 먹고 있죠
We're both getting older.
그런 제3의 선택지도 있지 물론
아주 잘 했네
That's the third option, of course.
That's great stuff.
제가 일기론 오늘 조크 정전협정이
성사되었다고 하던데요
I understand there's gonna be
a bit of a joke truce tonight.
적의의 중단이라
A cessation of hostilities.
물론이죠
저는 아무도 빈정거리지 않을 겁니다
Absolutely.
There will be no jokes from me.
그 사진도 언급하지 않을 거구요
I'm not going to mention
the photograph.
온라인 쇼핑을 하고 계셨나보죠?
Were you Internet shopping?
농담이에요
I'm joking.
아니 아예 하지 않는 게 좋겠죠
저기
Or rather, I'm not.
There we are.
Okay.
저는 이런 조찬 기도회에 있었죠
You know, I was at
that same prayer breakfast
한 한달전쯤에 말이에요
오 그래요?
- about a month or so ago.
- Oh, were you?
아주 훌륭한 애들이죠
아주 대단해요
- Aren't they great kids?
- They're great.
그리고 젊은 유권자로서
퇴역군인이 대통령이 된다는
And they seemed excited
as young voters
것에 대해 아주 흥미로워 하더군요.
about the possibility of
a veteran becoming president.
그게 꼭 저라는 건 아니구요
그래요
- Not necessarily me.
- Okay.
여성이 대통령이 되는 거에 대해서도
아주 흥미로워 하던데요
Well, they seemed very excited about the
possibility of a woman becoming president.
그게 꼭 부통령님이라는
건 아니죠
Not necessarily you.
제 강화된 국제 정책 책임이
중요해질 것 같아요
Well, my enhanced foreign
policy role will serve me well.
국제관계에 대해 잘 알고 있는
건 물론 중요한 일이죠
Hey, it is good to be on top
of international relations.
그러면 저같은 사람들이 목숨을
- Sure.
- So there are fewer opportunities
걸어야 할 위험이 줄어든다는 거니까요
for guys like me
to risk our lives.
물론이죠 물론이에요
Oh, absolutely.
Absolutely, yeah.
그리고 다리도 말입니다
그렇죠
- And limbs.
- Uh-huh.
이거 다 먹은 거야?
그럼 내가 먹을래
Are you not finishing this?
I'm gonna take it. Okay.
에이미 너 먹는 걸 좀
줄일 필요가 있어
Amy, you should
stop eating so much.
그게 갑자기 뭔 소린데?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
너 지금 스트레스성 폭식을 하고 있어
You're stress eating.
아니거든
그냥 디저트를 먹는 거야
I'm not.
I'm having dessert.
내 생각엔 사무실에서도 압박이
너를 너무 몰아붙이고 있는 것 같아
I think you're letting the pressures
of the office get to you.
넌 개인생활이 거의 없고
운동하러 가지도 않지
You barely have a life outside.
You don't go to the gym.
영화관에도 안 가고 거의
집에 있지조차 않지
You don't go to the movies.
You're barely at home.
그건 그래
That's true.
내가 고양이가 없어서 다행이지
I mean, I hope
I don't have a cat
왜냐면 그 불쌍한 새끼가
죽을 거거든
because, believe me,
that poor fucker's dead.
에이미 넌 데이트 좀 해야겠다
You need to date, Amy.
정치에 푹 빠진 정치오타쿠
하나 잡아, 샤워하는 놈으로
Find yourself a political
nerd who also showers.
난 그냥 널 위해서 하는 말이야
I'm just saying
I'm looking out for you.
니가 신경이상 뚱보가 될까봐
걱정되서 말야
I wouldn't want you to become
a fat, neurotic freak.
친구로서 충고하는 거야
Speaking as a friend.
오늘은 특별한 공연과 즐거움이
We have a lot of special
performances tonight
산더미처럼 준비도어 있습니다
대니 청 이 시키
- and a lot of fun ahead.
- Danny Chung.
그래서 걔가 탱크에서 사람을
끄집어 낸 게 뭐가 어쨌다는 거에요?
So he pulled a guy from a tank.
각하는 포로를 네 명이나 구해내셨다구요
You saved four guys
from captivity.
맞아 그리고 그 사람들은
화상을 입지도 않았다구
Yeah, and they weren't
burnt, by the way.
청이 구한 애들은 무슨 얼굴이
크리스마스 햄처럼 타버렸었다고
Chung's guy had a face
like a Christmas ham.
대니 청 주지사십니다!
Governor Danny Chung!
감사합니다
Thank you.
All right, thank you.
아시다시피 이 정권은 많은
도전에 직면해 왔습니다
You know, this administration
has faced many challenges.
하지만 지금까지
아무도 비트박스로
But until now,
nobody's thrown down
도전하진 않았죠
a beatbox challenge.
무슨 조또 인상적이지 않네요
That isn't impressive at all.
그냥 침뱉고 있는 거지?
예
- He's just spitting, right?
- Yeah.
수 수 숙녀분과 신사분들
L-l-ladies
and gentlemen,
미 미 미네소타가 여기 있습니다
M-m-m-m-minnesota's
in the house.
제가 물었죠 "그래서 그게 돈 때문이었어
아님 섹스 때문이었어?"
I said, "Well,
was it money or sex?"
그러니까 그가 이러더군요
"아냐 팍스뉴스에서 온 사람만
And he said,
"No, the guy from Fox News
멈춰서 방향을 물어보더라니까"
is the only one who stopped
and asked for directions."
감사합니다
Thank you.
잠시만 진지하게 말씀드리죠
To be serious
for just a moment,
우리 모두 자신의 의사에 반해서
I think we need to give
a big round of applause
오랫동안 잡혀 있었던 사람들을
to the vice president
for the part that she played
구출해내는데 그녀가 공헌한
in setting free
those young guys
바를 기리기 위해 큰 박수를 보내야 할 것 같습니다
who had been held against
their will for so long.
부통령 각하이십니다
감사합니다
Madam Vice President,
thank you.
Thank you.
물론 그녀가 한 일이라봐야 그냥
침실문을 열어둔 것 뿐입니다만
Of course, all she had to do
was unlock her bedroom door,
어쨌거나 감사합니다
but thanks anyway.
그래도 적어도 그사람들한테
냉담하게 굴지는 않았잖아요(휴대폰 본 자세)
Well, at least she didn't
look down her nose at 'em.
아시죠 그 뭘 볼때 말이죠
You know, when they're
looking for the thing.
아시는군요 하지만 감사합니다
You know, but thank you.
Okay. Okay.
경청해주셔서 매우 감사합니다
Thank you so much
for listening to me.
농담이 필요해, 농담이 필요하다구
감사합니다 좋은 밤 되세요
- I need a joke. I need a joke.
- Thank you. Good night.
Thank you.
신사 숙녀 여러분
짐 마우드였습니다
Jim Marwood,
ladies and gentlemen.
큰 박수를 부탁드립니다
Let's give it up for him.
메이트?
미트입니다
- Mate?
- Meat.
미트라고?
아뇨 뮤트요 뮤트
- Meat?
- No, mute. Mute.
뮤트라고 알았어
Mute. Here.
짐 마우드 당신을 도대체
어쩌면 좋을까요
Jim Marwood, what are we
gonna do with you?
음소거를 해버리고 싶은 스피커(하원의장)네요
I'll tell you, that's one speaker
I'd like to put on mute.
좋아요 제가 이걸 해볼 텐데
Okay, well, I'm gonna
give this a shot.
제가 셀린 디온이 아니라는
걸 염두에 둬 주시구요
You just need to keep in mind
that I'm not Selina Dion.
좋아요 그럼
Okay, well, you know what?
한번 해 볼까요
Let's hit it, boys.
♪ The problem
is all inside your head ♪
모든 문제는 니 머릿속에 있는 거야
♪ The problem
is all inside your head ♪
♪ Kent said to me ♪
켄트가 말했죠
♪ The answer is easy
if you take it logically ♪
논리적으로 생각하면
해답은 간단해
♪ The answer is easy
if you take it logically ♪
♪ If you analyze elections,
it's called psephology ♪
선거를 분석하면 선거학이라고 하지
♪ If you analyze elections,
it's called psephology ♪
♪ Kent says there's
50 ways to win in Denver... ♪
켄트가 말하길 덴버에서 이길
50가지 방법이 있다는군
* Kent says there's
50 ways to win in Denver... *
♪ Kent says there's 50 ways ♪
켄트가 말하길
♪ To win in Denver ♪
덴버에서 이길 50가지 방법이 있다는군
♪ You just say
you'll cut tax, Max ♪
그냥 세금을 깎는다고 말해
최대한으로 말야
♪ You just say
you'll cut tax, Max ♪
♪ Don't be elite, Pete ♪
엘리트처럼 굴지마 피트
♪ Kiss a fat baby, Abie ♪
뚱뚱한 애한테 키스를 해 애비
♪ Set yourself free ♪
자유로워져봐
♪ Don't be European, Ian ♪
유러피안처럼 굴지 마 이안
♪ Say screw France, Lance ♪
프랑스따윈 엿이나 먹으라고 해 랜스
♪ Maybe the Germans, Herman ♪
어쩌면 독일도 그러라 그러고 호일
♪ The Dutch, the Swedes ♪
네덜란드, 스웨덴
♪ Subsidize a bus, Gus ♪
버스에 보조금을 때려 거스
♪ Don't be pro-choice,
Joyce ♪
선택권에 대해 찬성하지 말고 조이스
♪ Don't be pro-choice,
Joyce ♪
♪ Not too much sex, Rex ♪
섹스도 좋지 않지 렉스
♪ Take it from me ♪
나한테서 가져가렴
♪ Make a pie chart, Art ♪
파이 차트를 만들어 아트
♪ Analyze the facts, Max ♪
사실을 분석해 맥스
♪ Don't live
in a palace, Alice... ♪
팰리스에 살아서도 안 돼지 엘리스
♪ Don't live
in a palace, Alice... ♪
완전 병맛이네
This is imbecilic.
맞습니다 완전 터무니없어요
You're right.
It's asinine.
아냐 계속 웃게나 라이언
No, keep smiling,
Mr. Ryan.
나도 웃는 척만 하고 있으니까
I'm smiling falsely.
So should you.
♪ Don't mention Israel,
Catherine. ♪
이스라엘은 언급도 하지 말고 캐서린
♪ Don't mention Israel,
Catherine. ♪
좋은 아침~
Good morning!
앨범이라도 내셔야 겠어요
You should cut an album.
상상이상이었지?
완전 학살하셨어요
- - Oh, can you imagine?
You killed it.
청보다도 더 잘하셨죠
You killed better
than Chung killed
그 자식은 실제로 사람을
죽였던 자식인데 말이에요
and he's actually killed.
저는 켄트 때문에
켄트가 좋아하는 척 하는 걸
I had to pretend
not to like it to Kent
따라하는 것처럼 좋아하는 척 해야 했는데
while pretending to like it like
he was pretending to like it,
켄트는 실제론 노랠 싫어했지만
저는 굉장히 좋았어요
but he didn't actually like it
and I actually really liked it.
오 안녕하십니까
Oh, hello, sir.
각하 어제 노래는 완전
입꼬리가 땡기게 만들더군요
Ma'am, your song last
night made my lips curl.
위로 말이죠
- Uh...
- Upwards.
좀 부탁드릴 게 있는데요
I have a small favor to ask.
물론이죠 뭘 도와드릴까요?
Okay, sure.
What can I do you for?
제 드림 메트릭 인구통계
프로그램이 곧 실행될 예정이라
Well, my Dream Metric demographic
program is about to launch
부통령님 직원 한명을 한 2주 정도
빌려주셨으면 합니다
and I would like to borrow a
member of your team for two weeks.
오, 댄 대려가게요?
Oh, you want Dan?
아뇨, 마이크가 필요합니다
No, I want Mike.
아뇨, 그렇지 않으실 걸요
댄을 대려가시는 게 좋을 거에요
Uh, no, you don't want me, sir.
You do want Dan.
댄이 정말 잘 해요
저한테 정말 좋은 아이디어가 많아요
- He's great.
- I've got a big bounce coming on.
완전 느껴진다니까요
I can feel it.
I'm like you.
아니 안돼요 마이크는 못 대려갑니다
No, uh-uh, you
can't take Mike.
내 언론 담당이라구요
He's my director
of communications.
지금 농담하는 거에요?
못 대려가요
Are you kidding me?
You can't have him.
포투스의 유럽 방문, 그
헬싱키 협정 말입니다
POTUS's European visit,
the Helsinki agreement...
그래서요?
가실 수 없게 되었습니다
- Yeah?
- He can no longer make it.
부채한도액 협상이 붕괴할
위험에 처했어요
Debt ceiling talks
are on the verge of collapse,
그래서 누군가 그 자리를
매꿔야만 하죠
so he needs someone
to go in his place.
국무부 장관이 아니면...
Now either that's
the Secretary of State or...
마이크, 다시 생각해보니
Mike, on second thought,
이 드림....
I think that
this whole Dream...
메트릭
- Metric.
드림 메트릭 머시기가
제법 그럴듯해 보여
Dream Metric thing
sounds kind of fantastic.
그렇지 않아?
그렇습니다 각하
- Don't you think?
- Yes, ma'am.
포투스께서 지시하신 거니까...
Comes from POTUS, so...
15분 후에 입구에서 보세 마이크
I'll see you down the hallway
in 15 minutes, Mike.
승선을 환영하네
I'll pipe you aboard.
각하, 유럽 여행 잘 다녀오십시오
Ma'am, enjoy your trip
to Europe.
고마워요
Thank you.
아 그리고 조나도 같이 갈 겁니다
Jonah will be making
the trip as well.
어 잠깐, 그게 무슨 소리에요?
Uh, wait.
What are you talking about?
내 언론 특보를 대려가면서
You're taking my director
of communications
조나 따위를 준다고?
and you're giving me Jonah?
포투스께서 내리신 명령입니다
This comes from POTUS.
각하, 각하 제발 절
대려가게 하지 말아주세요
Ma'am. Ma'am, please
don't let him take me.
전 그 숫자 캠프에 가고 싶지 않아요
I don't want to go
to numbers camp.
나도 별 수 없어 좀 놔봐
제발, 제발요
- I can't help you. Just let go.
- Please. Please.
아 씨바 놓으라고
Let go of me, all right?
딱 보니 니가 켄트한테
좋은 인상을 남겼나 보네
Obviously you made
an impression on Kent.
전 좋은 인상따윈 남기지 않는다구요
I don't make
impressions, ma'am.
전 말 그대로 제가 거기 없었다고
주장하는 사람들과 평생을 살았다구요
I've literally lived with people
who insist I was never there.
넌 프레스 브리핑 손도 대지 마 알겠지?
You give no press briefings.
Understood?
난 마이크가 되고 넌
못생긴 내가 되는거야
I become Mike,
you become an ugly me.
좋아
나는 신흥 미디어를 다룰게
Cool.
I'll handle new media.
각하 제가 대박 온라인
홍보를 해 드리겠습니다
Ma'am, I'm gonna get you
major online traction.
레딧, 텀블러, 붐
Reddit, Tumblr, boom.
그러든가 그냥 에어 포스 2에
있는 내 화장실만 쓰지 마
Whatever. Just don't use my
bathroom on Air Force Two.
거기 다른 화장실도 있었나요?
유럽!
- There's another bathroom?
- Europe!
그래 나도 알아 재밌을 거야
- Oh, mon dieu.
- Yeah, I know. It's gonna be fun.
정말 진심 재밌을 거에요
그래 굉장히 재밌을 거야
- Really, really fun.
- It'll be really fun.
그래서 말인데 정말 미안하지만 데이나랑
저녘 식사하긴 어려울 것 같아
Now, I'm so sorry, but I don't think we're
gonna be able to do the dinner with Dana.
아뇨 그럼 점심으로 옮길 수 있어요
그러도록 하죠
Oh, we can bring it forward to lunch.
Let's do that.
오 그러니까...
그쵸? 좋으시죠?
- Oh. Uh...
- Yeah? Yeah?
어 그래 그러자
좋죠? 좋죠? 좋아
- Oh. Yeah. Okay.
- Yeah? Yeah? Okay.
그래서 단도직입적으로 말하면
저는 페코리노 치즈를 수입하려고 해요
So cut to I'd set up a business
importing pecorino cheese.
페코리노 브랜드를 아시나요?
Are you familiar
with that brand of cheese?
어 그러니까...
파르메산 치즈랑 비슷한 거에요, 하지만 좀 다르죠
- Uh, I think...
- It's like parmesan, but it's different.
전혀 달라요
그... 그걸 뭐라고 표현했었지?
- They're very different.
- What's the word that you use to describe...
거무스름함
- A duskiness.
대단하지 않아요?
치즈를 거무스름하다고 한 적 있으세요?
Isn't that great?
Would you ever describe a cheese as dusky?
백만년이 지나도 못 그러겠지
난 그럴 것 같지 않네
Not in a million years, no.
I wouldn't do that.
그래서 파르메산 치즈를 수입한다고?
But so... so you import
parmesan?
페코리노요
미안해요 페코리노였죠
- Pecorino.
- I'm sorry, the pecorino.
투스카니에서 직수입하는 거에요
They're direct from Tuscany,
그 말은 플로렌스를 통해서
들어온다는 말이죠
so that means it comes in
through Florence.
만약 제가 시칠리안 공급자를
이용한다면, 물론 안 그러겠지만요
If I were to use a Sicilian
supplier, which I wouldn't,
제 간접비는 두배로 뛸 거에요
my overheads would double.
그리고 걔네들이 데이나가
And they would have
made her an offer
거절할 수 없는 제안을 했겠죠(대부 패러디)
that she couldn't refuse.
실제론 유제품 시장에 대한 마피아
관여는 극히 제한적이야
Actually, the mafia involvement
in the dairy industry is minimal.
니 말이 맞아 미안해
건방지게 굴 생각은 아니었어
You're right. I'm sorry, I
didn't mean to be flippant.
생각해봐 "대부"에는
치즈는 나오지 않는다구(나옵니다)
Think about it.
In "The Godfather," no cheese.
그래요 그렇죠
당연히 맞죠
- Yeah, you're right.
- You know I'm right.
붐!
이게 데이나의 캐치프레이즈에요
- Boom!
- That's her catchphrase.
한방 먹으셨네요
좀 더 조심하셨어야죠
She got you.
You got to be so careful.
그래
Okay.
게리
예?
- So, Gary.
- Yeah?
이 점심은 내가 너를 중요하게
생각한다는 걸 전하려는 자리야
This lunch is about me
saying that I value you.
그런 말을 들어서 얼마나
기쁜지 뭐라고 말해야할지 모르...
I cannot tell you, we are so
happy to hear you say that...
잠시 좀...
- If you could just...
- Ahem.
그리고 고맙다는 말을 하고 싶어
And I want to say thank you
니가 나한테 해준 거에 대해 말야
for all that you do for me.
굉장히 친절하시네요
Aw, that's so nice.
그리고 너한테 줄 선물이 있어
And I got you a little gift.
설마요!
정말이라니까
- No!
- Yes, I did.
오, 정말 친절하세요
Oh, that's so nice.
이것 좀 봐
새로운 리바이어던이야
Look at this.
A new Leviathan.
리바..
새 리바이어던이네요!
A Lev...
a new Leviathan!
아주 멋지지 않아?
Isn't that great?
내부 구성이 똑같은 거야 자기야?
Does it have
the same layout, honey?
저번에 그거 외우느라
생고생을 했잖아
Because it took you so long
to learn the other one.
아냐 괜찮아
새 구조정도야 쉽게 배울 수 있어
No, it's fine.
I can learn a new layout. It's fine.
내가 다른 종류를 구하는 게 좋았을까?
Do you wish that I had
gotten you a different kind?
아뇨 아뇨 그럴리가요
완전 마음에 들어요
No, no, no, no.
I love it.
♪ I love my new bag! ♪
내 새 가방은 대박이라네~
새 주머니를 몇 개 기워넣어도 되겠네요
I can just sew some new pockets in.
That's okay.
상징으로서 말이지
예 그렇죠
- 'Cause it's a symbol.
- Yeah.
너 자신을 위해서 말이지
예
- It's for you.
- Mm-hmm.
그거 내 전화야?
Is that for me?
예 맞네요 에이미 전화예요
Oh, yeah. That's for you.
It's Amy.
그래 무슨 일이야?
Hey, what's up?
켄트 송이 부정적인 영향을
불러일으켰어요
The Kent song has suddenly
gotten some negative traction.
"유럽에 대한 언급이"...
스피커로 돌릴게요
- "References to Europe"...
- I'm putting you on speaker.
셀리나 마이어 부통령이
부른 허접한 노래에 수록된
"References to Europe
in an ill-conceived song
유럽에 대한 언급은 대륙의 곳곳에서
performed by VP Selina Meyer
have sparked outrage
크나큰 분노를 불러일으켰다
뭐가 문젠데?
- in parts of the continent."
- What's the problem?
가사요
"유러피안처럼 굴지 마, 이안"
The lyrics
"don't be European, Ian,"
"프랑스 따윈 엿이나 먹으라고 해, 랜스"
그쪽 부분 전부요
"say screw France, Lance"...
that whole bit.
문제 링크를 아이패드로
보내드릴게요
I'm sending the alert links
to your iPad.
개리 미안한데 내 아이패드 좀 줄래?
Excuse me, Gary.
Can I have my iPad?
가지고 있어?
그럼요
- Do you have that?
- Oh, right here.
여기요 죄송합니다
고마워
- Here you go. Sorry.
- Thanks.
니가 너 자신을 알아가는 동안
You know, while you're getting
to know your own mind,
나도 너의 나머지 부분을 알아가는 것 같아
I'm getting to know
the rest of you.
그리고 난 그게 아주 좋아
And Mama likes.
미안한데
아주 좋다구
- Excuse me.
- Mama like it.
미안해
개리 정말 미안한데, 잠깐만
I'm so sorry.
Excuse me, Gary, just for a second.
내 패스워드가 뭔지 모르겠어
넌 뭔지 아니?
I don't know what my password is.
Do you know what it...?
그건 4G입니다 와이파이는 필요 없습니다 각하
하지만 신호가 다 있잖아
- It's 4G. You don't need a Wi-Fi, ma'am.
- But the signals are all here.
와이파이를 다 꺼버려야 돼요
You know what you got to do
is shut the Wi-Fi off.
그래야 4G로 연결이 되죠
제 말이 맞다니까요
That forces it into 4G.
You know I'm right.
그래, 그건 잠깐 그만두자
어떻게 해야 하는건지 모르겠어
- Okay, let's not do that.
- I'm not sure how to do that.
안돼 안돼 그거 기밀사항이야
아무것도 안 건드릴거야
- No, no, no. That's confidential.
- I won't touch anything.
아무것도 안 건드린다구
웁스, 이란이랑 전쟁을 시작해버렸네
I won't touch anything.
Oops, I just started a war with Iran.
농담이에요
아쉽게도 전혀 웃기지 않네요
- Joke.
- That's not even remotely funny.
그냥 제 좋은 농담 중 하나에요
That's just one
of my classic jokes.
칼라마리 즈키니?
오 그건 게리거에요
- Calamari and zucchini?
- Oh, that would be for Gary here.
예 여기있어요
그리고 올리브 좀 드시겠습니까?
- Okay, here you go.
- And maybe some olives?
오 안돼 안돼 이런
저리 가요!
- Oh, no, no, no, no!
- Get out!
오 젠장할
Oh, God.
우리의 유럽 방문이 방금
Well, our European visit
지옥으로 향하는 편도열차 + 귀환
으로 바뀌었어
just got turned into a one-way
trip to hell and back.
그럼 왕복이잖아요
있잖아!?
- That's actually a return.
- You know what?
제발 한 2초라도 좀 닥쳐줄래요?
Could you just shut it
just for like two seconds?
가보셔야 되지 않나요?
그래 점심을 좀 빨리 끝내야 겠어
- Why don't we go?
- Yeah, we've got to cut this lunch short.
하지만 가방은 평생 갈거니까
점심이 뭔 소용이야
But, you know, you're gonna have
your bag forever, so what the fuck?
좋은 오후입니다 여러분
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
드림 메트릭은 바로
이 순간 시잘됩니다
Dream Metric begins
at this second.
오늘이 바로 그라운드 제로입니다
마이크
Today is ground zero.
Mike.
그렇군요
Right.
이건 바로 미국의 목차입니다
This is the index to America.
이건 사람들이 그들 자신도 채
It will let us know
how people will vote
알기 전에 어떻게 투표할지 알려줄 겁니다
before they even
know themselves.
이 프로그램은 우리가 사고하는 방법에
This program revolutionizes
the way we think
대해 생각하는 방법을 혁명적으로 바꿀겁니다
마이크
about the way we think.
Mike.
아주 멋지네요
It's exciting.
한시간 전 독일 수상은
"Within the last hour,
the German chancellor
사건에 대한 그의 실망을 나타냈다
expressed his disappointment
at the remarks."
씨바 지가 뭔데?
Who the hell
does he think he is?
라 몽드의 조지 데니스는
"'George Dennis' of 'Le Monde'
부통령이 전형적인 미국
촌뜨기라고 논평했다
called the vice president
a typical American hick."
제 생각에 조지 드니스인 것 같네요
I think it's pronounced
Georges Denis.
누굴보고 촌뜨기래
엿이나 먹어라 드파르디외(프랑스 배우)
I'm not a hick.
Screw you, Depardieu.
제 생각엔 레딧과 텀블러에
올라가면서
I think it just got
on Reddit and Tumblr
거기서 폭발적으로 퍼진 것 같습니다
and just exploded from there.
그 단어들이 굉장히
익숙하게 느껴지는데
Uh, those words
sound mighty familiar.
조나?
Jonah?
전 그냥 그 노래가 너무 좋아서요
I just liked the song so much.
그리고 제 생각엔 각하께서도
홍보를 하고 싶으실 것 같았구요
And I thought
you wanted it out there,
그래서 제가 그냥 퍼뜨린 거죠
so I just put it out there.
당장 내려
Get off the plane.
예?
What?
당장 뛰어내리라고
각하 벌써 활주로 주행중입니다
- Get off of the plane.
- Ma'am, we're taxiing.
조또 내가 신경이나 쓸것 같애
당장 내 비행기에서 내리라고
I don't give a shit.
Get the fuck off my plane.
당장 내 비행기에서
내리란 말이다!
Yeah, get the fuck
off of my plane.
니놈 시키가 그걸 텀블에
올리다니 정말 믿을 수가 없군
I cannot believe that you
put that out on Tumble.
아뇨, 텀블런데요
- No, Tumblr.
- Okay.
엔진 시동 꺼~!
조나 좀 비행기 밖으로 던져버릴 수 있을까요?
- Stop the engines!
- Can we get Jonah off the plane, please?
일나
Get up.
니 특권은 싸그리 말소될거야
All of your privileges
are gonna be removed.
알겠습니다 하지만 주차공간만은
그래 그것도 몰수할거야
- Okay, but not the parking.
- Yeah, the parking.
잠깐 뭐? 니가 주차공간까지 있다고?
더이상은 아니죠
- Wait, what? You have parking?
- Not anymore.
그래 이 순간으로 끝이야
하지만 전 차도 없었다구요
- Yeah, not anymore.
- But I didn't even own a car.
방금 닛산 큐브를 2년간
리스 계약했단 말입니다
I just had to sign a two-year
lease for the Nissan Cube.
당장 끄집어내
잠깐 내 가방이 아직 저기 있어
- Get him off.
- Okay, guys, my bag is in the hold.
쟤 가방이 큰가?
게리
- Does he have a big bag?
- Gary.
좋아
좀 나으신가요?
- Okay.
- Better?
이제 괜찮아
이제 괜찮습니다
- It's all good.
난 괜찮아
완전히 괜찮으시죠
- I'm fine.
- Totally fine.
좋아
Great.
이 비행 얼마나 걸리지?
How long is this flight?
숫자란, 결코 끝이 없어
그렇지 않나?
Numbers, they never
end, do they?
하지만 그게 매혹적인 점이지
But that's what's
good about them...
계속되니까 말야
they keep going.
Aw.
자살기도자 감시리스트에
올라가야 할 것 같은데
He should really be
on suicide watch.
그래, 이 고통을 끝까지
이어가도록 확실히 해 두자구
Yeah, make sure
he goes through with it.
이건 라틴계 투표죠 맞나요?
That's the Latino vote, right?
그거 말이에요?
That thing?
마이크 이리 좀 오게
옛써
- Mike, my office.
- Yes, sir.
펜
Pen.
저번에 거기서 닛산 큐브를
리스한 사람인데요
I leased a Nissan Cube
from you the other day.
제가 더이상 필요하지 않다면
저한테 무슨 선택권이 있나요?
What are my options
if I don't need it anymore?
혹 반품할 수는 없나요?
Can I just give that back?
안됀다구요?
No?
Paper.
♪ Help the oil lobby, Bobby ♪
오일 로비를 도와줘 바비
♪ Don't piss off
Wall Street, Pete ♪
월스트리트랑 쌈박질
하지 말고 피트
♪ Don't piss off
Wall Street, Pete ♪
♪ Don't mention
Israel, Catherine... ♪
이스라엘 얘기는 꺼내지도
말아 캐서린
* Don't mention
Israel, Catherine... *
♪ Get out of DC ♪
DC를 떠나는 거야
♪ Steve. ♪
스티브
Yeah!